// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Fatigue is caused because of formation and depositing of which among the following acids in Muscles?",
        answer: "Lactic Acid",
        options: [
            "Lactic Acid",
            "Acetic acid",
            "Citric Acid",
            "Pyruvic acid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Bile is secreted by which of the following cells?",
        answer: "Hepatocytes",
        options: [
            "Hepatocytes",
            "Brown Fat Cells",
            "Lymphocytes",
            "Somatocytes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which among the following is aromatic dried flower buds of a tree ?",
        answer: "Clove",
        options: [
            "Black pepper",
            "Clove",
            "Cumin",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which among the following virus is also called as “Hit & Hide” Virus?",
        answer: "RSV Virus (respiratory syncytial virus )",
        options: [
            "RSV Virus (respiratory syncytial virus )",
            "Dengue virus",
            "Influenza virus",
            "HIV virus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which among the following is not a carnivorous plant?",
        answer: "Marsh Mallow",
        options: [
            "Pitcher plant",
            "Venus Fly Trap",
            "waterwheel plant",
            "Marsh Mallow"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which branch of biology is known for the study of microscopic organisms?",
        answer: "Microbiology",
        options: [
            "Microbiology",
            "Cytology",
            "Taxonomy",
            "Spermology"
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "In what form do fungi store food",
        answer: "Oil and glycogen",
        options: [
            "Lipid",
            "Starch",
            "Oil and glycogen",
            "Protein"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which sugar is present in RNA?",
        answer: "Ribose",
        options: [
            "Hexose",
            "Ribose",
            "Fructose",
            "Glucose"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is not a cause of Food Poisoning?",
        answer: "Yersinia pestis",
        options: [
            "Salmonella",
            "Campylobacter",
            "E. coli & Shigella",
            "Yersinia pestis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is analogous to mesosome of bacteria?",
        answer: "Mitochondria of eukaryotes",
        options: [
            "Mitochondria of eukaryotes",
            "Golgi apparatus of eukaryotes",
            "Lysosomes of eukaryotes",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
];